MAMOKOINIHI VERONICA KUENENE

Email - mkuenene@gmail.com

Dear Sir/Madam

I am applying for the outreach specialist position advertised on search engines. I am a self-

motivated and hard-working digital marketer seeking employment in an environment that

requires analytical skills, creativity, problem-solving and general online marketing knowledge. I

have five years of experience as a content writer in the following niches: lifestyle, education,

astrology, health, real estate and many more. Due to my extensive experience working across

multiple industries, I have good verbal and written communication skills.

I have taken an email marketing course; therefore, I am aware of the terminology and nuances

of email marketing and have experience with platforms such as Mailchimp and Sender. In

addition, I have extensive experience writing SEO-optimized content using keywords related to

the client's product and service. I also know Google Analytics and various SEO tools such as

Ahrefs, SEMRush, Moz, and Google Keyword Planner, which I use to conduct keyword research

to produce SEO content and conduct SEO audits. I also have a working knowledge of link-building

techniques to improve the website's visibility on the result pages.

I also have experience working as a content writer for a digital marketing agency, reducing long-

form texts from brochures and whitepapers into shorter articles. In my career, I have also been

exposed to proofreading and editing brochures, writing blog articles, and writing articles on

various platforms for link building purposes. I also publish content on Medium for personal

blogging. I am articulate and pay close attention to writing and proofreading details. In addition,

due to extensive freelance work and working from home, I manage my time well and always

deliver work on time.

Yours Faithfully

Mamokoinihi Veronica Kuenene

# Mamokoinihi Veronica Kuenene

# Digital Marketer

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

mkuenene@gmail.com



**8** +27 65976 7356

## **SKILLS**

- Canva
- Creative writing
- Copywriting
- **SEO**
- Social Media Marketing
- **Email marketing**
- Google analytics

## **ATTRIBUTES**

- Project management
- People skills
- **Planning**
- Creativity
- Problem solving
- Organizational skills

# **HOBBIES**

- Reading
- Learning
- Charity work

I am a hard-working, diligent digital marketer with 5 years of experience. I have worked on a lot of different projects, one of which was a fundraising campaign that raised 15% more money from donors than the year before. During this campaign, I was a content writer, a social media marketer, a video editor, and a designer for social media templates.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **LEAD GENERATOR DIGITAL**

Digital Marketing Intern February 2023 - Present

- Optimizing the client's Google Business Profile for local search
- Link building
- Local SEO

## **ACADEMIC CONTENT WRITER**

Berea Technical College

November 2020 - Present

Producing content for higher education student in the faculty of built and engineering.

#### DIGITAL MARKETING APPRENTICE

Inkfish Digital Marketing

January 2019 – August 2019

- Proofreading and editing blog post before publication.
- Conducting content and SEO audit to check general site performance against the set KPIs.
- Writing content for blogs in different niches and for different social media platforms.
- Conduct keyword research and check the performance of the chosen keywords in website traffic and ranking.
- Run SEO and content competitor analysis to check the performance of competing companies.

#### **BUILDING TECHNICIAN**

**Master Services** 

October 2012 - December 2013

- Preparing engineering and architectural drawings using AutoCAD and ArchiCAD.
- Prepared bill of quantities and construction schedule for construction
- Coordinating with building suppliers for the supply of building materials.
- Coordinating with finance department to facilitate payment of labourers and suppliers.
- Quantity take-off from drawings.
- Plan and execute daily work on site.
- Lead maintenance department for the enhancement or modification following through to their successful completion.

#### **JUNIOR SITE FOREMAN**

#### Y Construction

March 2012 - August 2012

- Carry out survey work needed for construction projects.
- General site supervision.
- Setting out of structures
- Fill in daily labourers attendance record and activity forms.
- Ordering and following up on site material deliveries.
- Supervising general building and concreting work.
- Quality control.

## **CAD TECHNICIAN**

United Consultancy Services February 2011 – February 2012

- Preparing engineering drawings using AutoCAD
- Assist in surveying work needed for the design and construction of Public Works projects.
- Acts as an Inspector for construction work.
- Drafted detailed drawings and plans for new sewer, stormwater and water supply system designs of Public Works project.
- Quality control.
- Compiled drawings and layout according to required media & specification.

### **EDUCATION**

# **BIng Civil Engineering**

University of Johannesburg 2014 - 2020

# **Diploma in Construction Engineering**

Lerotholi Polytechnic 2005-2010

## PERSONAL DEVELOPMENT

- University of California, Davis's Professional Certificate in Search Engine
  Optimization Coursera (2020)
- Facebook's Professional Certificate in Introduction to Social Media Marketing - Coursera (2020)
- Facebook's Professional Certificate in Social Media Management -Coursera (2020)
- University of California, Davis's Professional Certificate in Website
  Optimization Client Report Project Coursera (2020)
- University of California, Davis's Professional Certificate in Advanced Content and social tactics to optimize SEO – Coursera (2020)